BRAC Chicago Files 5488 A
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BRAC Chicago Files
1857-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees (BRAC)
5488 A
107 cubic feet
103 linear ft.
Records.
3120239
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 20, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 20, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees was organized in 1899, and it was the largest single railroad organization for employees who devoted a majority of their time to clerical work of any description including chief clerks, foremen, train announcers, gatemen, checkers; parcel, baggage, and storeroom employees; dock and pier workers; train and engine crew callers; timekeepers; paymasters; freight inspectors; rate and tariff compilers; weigh masters; ticket clerks and sellers; operators of all office and station equipment devices; telephone and switchboard operators; and all employees occupying or performing duties similar to those mentioned. After three months of experience in clerical work employees of both genders, with good moral character, became eligible for membership. The union secured increases in wages and better working conditions for its members.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5488: BRAC Records 5488 A & B mf: BRAC Guides on Microfilm 5488 B: BRAC Records 5488 C: BRAC Additional Records 5488 D: BRAC Additional Records 5488 MB: BRAC Memorabilia
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes.
3120239
- ORT Minutes, 1923-1962 (Box 1, Folder All)
- MBD Minutes, 1941-1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- MBD Minutes, 1954-1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- MBD General Ledger Accounts (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board Proceedings, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ORT Constitution, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ORT Constitution, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ORT Constitution, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ORT: Report of Proceedings-35th Regular Session of Grand Division, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ORT: Report of Proceedings-35th Regular Session of Grand Division, Volume II, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- ORT Board of Directors and MBC Report-35th Regular Session, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- TCU: Report of Vice Presidents-37th Regular Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- TCU: Report of the Board of Directors-37th Regular Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- TCU: Report of Grand Secretary and Tresurer, L.H. Freeman-37th Regular Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- TCU: Report of President G.H. Leighty-37th Regular Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- TCU: Highlights of Leighty's presidency, 1947-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- TCU: Board Proceedings-37th Regular Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ORT: Board of Proceedings, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- ORT: Board of Proceedings, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- ORT: Board of Proceedings, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- ORT: Board of Proceedings, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- ORT: Board of Proceedings, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Circular File, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- BRAC Legislative Capsule, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- T-C Division Changes, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Clearing files and Preparation for Moving to BRAC Headquarters, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ORT-TCU-TC Division BRAC History (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  no date
- ORT-TCU Momentos (Box 4, Folder 6)
- ORT-TCU Headquarters Purchase-Dedication-Sale, 1952-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Mailing Lists for Organizational Charges, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- TCU-BRAC Merger and Agreement, Proposal, and BRAC Constitution (Box 4, Folder 9)
- BRAC Grand Executive Council, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- BRAC Travel Industry, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- BRAC Annual Educational Conference, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- BRAC International Affairs-Team Managers Assignments, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Biographical Sketches-Officers and Staff, 1948-1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees-Employment (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees-Advance Expense and Loans, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees-Instructions, 1953-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- T-C Division, BRAC-Minutes, 1964-1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- T-C Division BRAC Grand Officers Listing (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Transfer GS&T Expenses and Funds, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Moving Expenses, 1953-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Retirement, 1963-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Actuarial Study of Staff-Retirement Plan TCU, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Sale of Home, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Vacation, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Grand Officers-Staff-Employees: Board of Directors Approval of Health and Welfare Coverage, 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- BRAC Building Company, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- BRAC Title Holding Company, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- BRAC Auditing and Bonding, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- BRAC Budget, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- BRAC Disaster Relief Fund, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- BRAC Grand Lodge Expenses, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- FEC Hardship Fund, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- BRAC Organization Fund, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Death Benefit Study of BRAC, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Authorization for Presidential Contributions, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Authorization for Promotional Expenses, 1949-1956 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Freeman, L.H. Grand Secretary-Tresurer, 1957-1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Lowry, A.R. President, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  July 1968 thru 1968-71
- W.R. Drysart,Jr., 1963-1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Executive Assistant July 1968; Deputy President 1963-1971
- Board of Directors-General Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Board of Directors-Personnel-Salaries-Charges-Expenses, 1952-1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- P.H. Gignac, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- F.V. Goldsmith, Member of Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- T.C. Robinson, Chairman, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- R.M. Skelly, Member, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- W.E. Waters, Secretary, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Finance Committee-General, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- BRAC General Lodge Finance Committee-General, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Vice Presidents-USA and Canada-General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- R.K. Anthis, Vice President- General Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- S.G. Bishop, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- D.A. Bobo, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- F.E. Easterbrook, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- A.A. Hutchinson, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- D.C. Jones, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1953-1969 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- R.I. Kilroy, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- R.O. Norton, Vice Presidents - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- A.O. Olsen, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- S.Z. Placksin, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- J.I. Steed, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- H.D. Smith, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1950-1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- R.C. Smith. Vice President - General Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- R.J. Woodman, Vice President - Genreral Correspondence, 1955-1968 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- J.F. Young, Vice President - General Correspondence, 1946-1968 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- S.G. Bishop Reports, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- D.A. Bobo Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- R.I. Kilroy Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- R.O. Norton Reports (Box 5, Folder 51)
- S.Z. Placksin Reports, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- H.D. Smith Reports, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- R.C. Smith Reports (Box 5, Folder 54)
- J.W. Whitehouse Reports (Box 5, Folder 55)
- J.M. Willemin Reports, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Attorneys-General Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Attorneys Decisions- E.J. Hickry- L.P. Schoene, 1956-1969 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Attorneys Fees-Informational, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Attorneys-Legal Bills BRAC, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Organizers - General Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 61)
- BRAC Departmental and Staff Personnel - General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Echols, D.T. Executive Assistant to President, 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Howard, R.J. Grand Secretary's Department, 1959-1969 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Cole, L.A. Executive Assistant to President, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Research and Statistical Set-up, 1946-1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Leighty, C.E. Assistant Statistician (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bureau Set-up, 1950-1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Flynn, T.W. - BU Staff Assistant, 1962-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Forbes, R.F. - BU Staff Assistant, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hamilton, I.E. - BU Staff Assistant, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Howes, W.H. - BU Staff Assistant, 1963-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Kingsbury, L.M. - BU Staff Assistant, 1953-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Payne, Carroll - BU Staff Assistant, 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Rose, Frank C. - Director Bureau of Claims and Grievances, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Walsh, J.E. - BU Staff Assistant, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- NLAB Labor Member JWW-Assets, 1953-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Whitehouse, J.W. Vice President, member NLAB, 1950-1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Willeman, J.M. Member of Supplemental Board, 1951-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- BRAC Grand Officers Lodge Employees Agreement (Local 1603 Roosevelt Lodge) - General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- BRAC Grand Officers Lodge Employees Agreement, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  5/1/68 - Original Memo/Letter Agreements/Interpretations
- TC-Division-BRAC Grand Lodge Agreement Dispute - B. Kempf claim for overtime as senior employee, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Office Employees, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Employees Regional Offices - M. Agulnik - Montreal Office, 1953-1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Brune, Lorna(Mrs.) Stenographer-Clerk, 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  12/10/60-69
- Collins, Patricia (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Dekeergieter, Henri, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  9/3/68 1968-69
- Dysart, Mark, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  6/8/1968
- Fraser, Desmond, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Johnson, Marilyn, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Kempf, Bernadice(Mrs.) Stenographer-Clerk, 1954-1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  5/16/66 1954-69
- Klemme, Melvin, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Knight, Betty R.(Mrs.) Stenographer-Washington Office, 1955-1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Menas, Mildred, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Myers, Dorothy M. (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Parker, Gertrude, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Riggle, Julia(Mrs.) Stenographer-File Supervisor, 1953-1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  7/25/1949
- Royce, Eugene R. - Typist Multilith Operator, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Sanchez, S., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Seghi, Jean (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Sneed, Betty Stenographer-Clerk, 1953-1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  11/5/1952
- Mrs. J.O. Walker - Secretary Division 7, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Wiegal, Ednamae - Stenographer-Clerk, 1963-1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  7/5/1955
- Payroll Information Forms, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Payroll Time Books, 1919-1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- General Officers' Associations (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Grand and General Officers Meeting, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  May 6,7,8 1969
- Grand Officers and Staff Meeting, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 21, 1969 Chicago, Illinois
- Directories National and International - Labor Unions USA and Canada, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Labor Organizations - General, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Organizations - General, 1955-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Conference of Transportation Trades - Congress of Railway Unions, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association(CRLEA) Ottawa Office, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association (CRLEA)- General, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association (CRLEA)- Assessments, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association (CRLEA)- ByLaws, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association (CRLEA) Research Bureau - General Correspondence and Assessments, 1959- 1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Canadian Railway Labour Executive Association (CRLEA) National Joint/Provincial Joint/Legislative Committee, 1953-1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Associated Non-Operating Railway Unions - Canadian Conference Committee, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Associated Non-Operating Railway Unions - Canadian Negotiating Committee, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- RLEA, 1959-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Railway Labor Executives Association - Assessments and Percentage Allocation of Cost, 1947-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Charges - RLEA Stenographer Service and Postage, 1955-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- RLEA History and By-Laws, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- RLEA: Equipment-Office and Printing Plant, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- RLEA - Financial Statements (Monthly), 1952-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- RLEA General Fund - Yearly, 1959-1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- RLEA - Meetings and Agenda, 1958-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- RLEA - List of Members, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- RLEA - Minutes of Meetings, 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- RLEA: Salaries-Elections-Employment-Officers and Staff, 1950-1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- RLEA Study Committee - A.R. Lowry, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- RLEA Study Committee - A.R. Lowry, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- International Brotherhood Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Brotherhood of Railway Airline and Steamship Clerks, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Transportation Communication Division - BRAC, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Allied Services Division of Railway Patrolmen Security Officers - BRAC, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- American Train Dispatchers Association, 1959-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- American Train Dispatchers Association, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood Electrical Workers, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood Fireman and Oilers, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood Maintenance Way Employees, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Organization Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Railway Employees Department AFL-CIO, 1953-1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Sleeping Car Porters, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Seafarers International Union of North America, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood Railroad Signalmen, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- United Transportation Union, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1918-1968 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- BRAC Bulletins (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Outlaw Orgainizations, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Outlaw Organizations - Railroad Pension Groups, 1958-1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Recapitulation and Exhibits, 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- International Labor Organizations, 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Air Line Pilots Association, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Transport, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Confederation National Trade Unions, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Engineers, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- International Brotherhood Longshoremen (Box 9, Folder 27)
- International Longshoremen's Association, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Maritime Trades Department AFL-CIO, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- National Maritime Union of America, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Transport Workers Union of America, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- United Transportation Service Employees, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- ITF Convention Vienna, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- AFL-CIO General Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- AFL-CIO Conference on Transportation Trades, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Per Capita Tax, 1953-1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Political Contributions, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO No Raiding Agreement, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Cases - Mediated by G.E. Leighty, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Cases (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Canadian Labour Congress, 1962-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Affiliates - Canadian Labour Congress, 1961-1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Charitable Orgainizations - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- American Heart Association, 1953-1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Association of American Railways, 1964-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- American Red Cross, 1952-1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Congress of Railroad Unions, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Labor Bureau of Middlewest, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- International Labor Press of America, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Ladies Auxiliary - TCU, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Midwest Research Bureau, 1954-1965 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Morse Telegraph Club of America, 1963-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- National Museum of Transport, 1959-1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- National Safety Council, 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Students for Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- United Fund, 1946-1966 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Labor - Newspaper General Corrspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Labor Coop Educational and Public Society Certificate of Membership - ARL Trustees for TCU, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Labor - Newspaper Contract for Printing, 1954-1962 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Labor - Newspaper Special Editions Policy, 1951-1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Labor Newspaper - Management, 1951-1966 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Labor Newspaper-Assessments-Percentage Allocation-each organization, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Canadian Railwaymen - General, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Labor Newspaper: Audits, 1954-1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Labor Newspaper: Building, 1956-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Labor Newspaper: By-Laws and Amendments, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Labor Newspaper: Minutes, Board of Directors, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Labor Newspaper: Minutes-Owners, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Labor Newspaper: Pension Plan - Employees, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Labor Newspaper: Purchase Press, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- BRC-ORT Joint Relations Agreement - Teletype, 1935-1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- ATDA-ORT Joint Relations Agreement - General Correspondence, extra copies of agreement, 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Jurisdiction - General Correspondence, 1944-1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Possible Merger: BRT-ORC-ORC&B-TCU, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Jurisdictional Disputes BRC-ORT, 1938-1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- BRC-ORT(TCU) Jurisdictional Dispute, 1922-1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- BRC-TCU Jurisdictional Dispute (Box 12, Folder 1)
- BRAC-TCU Merger - Canadian portion, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- TCU-BRAC Merger Agreement, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  2/21/1969
- TCU-BRAC Merger TC-Division-BRAC Canadian Certification, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- TCU-BRAC Merger, T-C Division, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Second Ballot Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- MWE-ORT Tower and Leverman (Box 12, Folder 7)
- BRAC Merger Disputes Under Section 2.11 of Agreement, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- BRAC Merger Disputes Under Section 2.11 of Agreement, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Constitutions - Copies, 1895-1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- General - Dissidents Supervision and Control (Box 12, Folder 11)
- BRAC Constitution - General Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Constitution - General, 1956-1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Constitution Article 5 - Section 1-G Ratification of National Movements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Resolutions and Amendments, 1949-1960 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rulings - Constitution, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Ruling Article XI Section 16-D, 1959-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Division 3 and 17, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Division 3 and 19 over representative employees on Toledo and Ohio Central Division of NY System, 1959-1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Division 4 and 16 - Allocation of Positions 22nd St. Tower, Sioux City, Iowa, 1957- 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Division 13 and 14, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Divisions 18-26 over assignment of work in consolidated agency Edwardsville, Illinois, 1966- 1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Divisions 25-72 over allocation of work at Corpus Cristi, Texas, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Division 26 and 18 Gibson City, Illinois, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Divisions 26 and 37 over allocation of tricks, N. Kansas City, Birmingham, and Block 222, Mo, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dipute between Divisions 28-58 re filling vacancy "Q" office, Montgomery, Alabama, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Ruling Article XI, Section 16-D: Dispute between Divisions 46-59 re allocation of forces 6 Agencies=1 Relay Office and 3 Towers, 1969- 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Charges against Officers and Suspension from Office (In Division Order), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Charges Against Officers and Suspension from Office - Copeland, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Charges Against Officers Vieaux vs Ruff, Krystofiak and Cranch, 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Charges Against Officers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Suspension of Officers - Division 14, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Charges Against Officers R.T. Phillips - Suspension, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Division 27, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Charges Against Officers - Division 32, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Charges Against Officers - Division 50, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Charges Against Officers - Division 53, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Trial Board - Baumgarter vs. Fisher, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Trial Board - Ward vs. Kinisky, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Charges Against General Chairman Ward by Baumgarter, Eatman, Morrow, and Panick, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Charges Against Officers - Baumgarter and Panick vs. D.W. Ward: signing agreements without consent of General Committee, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Charges Against Officers Baumgarter-Panick vs. D.W. Ward: Violation of Article XII, Section 1-2-16-18 of International Constitution, 1968- 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Charges Against Officers - Misconduct as specified in Constitution Article XII paragraphs 1-2-3-15-16 Baumgarter vs. Fisher, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)